Hello friends, today we are going to talk about
ICC Lombard General Nations Company Limited
and the company has
declared excellent results. So today we will
look at its results. Friends,
its results have been declared by the company
and today we will do an analysis of the internals
and compare them. So let's
look at the middle column for December and compare them. So let's
first see that the total income of the company was
4362 crores.
If we compare it quarterly, we
see more than 20% increase in the company's income,
that is, the company is continuously expanding its business.
Now let's also look at its total expenses. It was
around 626 crores in December
and around 3976 crores in the March 2020 quarter. Now we will also look at
its tax on profit.
In the March 2020 quarter, the profit was 410
crores. If we
look at the December 22 quarter, the company
's profit was around 465 crores and in March it was
72 crores.
352 crores had
increased to 436 crores. If we compare it quarterly, then
we are seeing a
great growth of more than 39% in the profit of the company. If we
compare it quarterly, then
we are seeing a great growth of more than 30% in the profit of the company, that is, a
very great result by the company. Along with this, the
company declared a dividend of Rs 5.5, so
in the March 2019 quarter it was ₹636 paise
and in the December
1838 quarter it was
₹890 paise
and now if we look at its result financially, then
if we look at the last final year i.e.
ending March quarter, so if we see now, the
total income of the company was
around 1619 crores in the whole year and if we
look at the financial year ending on 23, then in the same year the
total of the company was less,
1894 crores. If we do so, then
we are seeing a great growth of more than 12% in the income of the company
and if we
look at its profit, then the
profit of the last month was ₹231
Approximately Rs. 729 crores and if we
look at the current finances, the profit of the company has been Rs.
729 crores, if we compare it, then
we are seeing a great growth of more than 36% on the profit of the company, that is, if we
look at the profit, the
company has been doing very well, if you
look at the EPF, then in the last financial year,
UPS was
Rs. 2591 and the current finance was Rs.
21 paise, so friends, these were the same Lumber
General Company Limited quarters